friends Welcome to Profit Mantra
Friends in this video we will see ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Phantom Type
Hello friends this is the chart of the last 4 years of the company
because the IPO
of the company came in 2017 in the copper period
in the last 4 years the company has
given returns of up to 116 percent to its share price If you see the chart then it
is written in straight line
in a hybrid, we have such a chart above, so for 16
years the flag has gone up with little consistency
and see the stock
of ₹16 100 is not only Virat 1470
in the last four years, you can say that the money has doubled
in the temple but the share has not given any returns, let's
see the front of the company in the last year
friends, if you see then you can say 1769
0670 and you will be
happy because if you see then 1626
element is also available now in less than half the time
and the local has shifted to 1200  It has
happened that John R Jun21 61.945 center has
been arranged, if
we see the share holding pattern then we will see
from motor 51.8 central public 58.13 versus
application, we have the data record of a company,
on four face a mar 2021,
all these girls on share1 tweet1
2019 and ₹3.50 on 619 June 2019 50
paisa on 28 October 2018 Durga Puja kaise on 4
July 2018, such a company contributed, so the
hair oil is free 100%, they should
not keep it on this topic only,
hello friends, as the name of the company is
that General Insurance Company Limited, the company does
insurance, you will see John Marg
3420 26.2 million policy, this company has 30
and the company does all types of policies, car
insurance, two wheeler, sports, travel,
timer, Dinesh
A Prominent Insurance, cyber insurance
and recently the company has launched policy in Corolla Kavach, due to
complete,
I am lagging behind the market 65  9663 falls
to toffee 46 bills 167 rupees are division in
0.8 per cent RC Shyarauli 216 and still
₹10 friends this always hits you
₹10 failed because you had invested today
you can
get ₹10 in future by increasing share quantity, if you
see this process then the company
is almost everywhere a leading company, the district and
good profit growth in the last five years is
23.15 percent tax gifted company and
David has also taken his 1658, it will reach 14%, if
you see then stop this spread is doing
60 fits from the previous wipes temple jewellery, at
this time the basis is running included under income
of 405 21 crore promoters have reduced their
holding in the last two-three years - 1404, if you
look at the quarterly result then the
company's sense in Edison 2018 which is 2500 crore and on
quarterly basis  But if you see, in March 2018,
this figure is seen to be 3163 crores,
so if you see on the basis of the previous quarter, then
this figure in April, we will see that the business of the company is
made on contract basis,
new figures are being seen
in every quarter and the operating profit
in Dishoom 2008 was 340 crores, which will be in 2021-15
because in this year of the company, due to
this modern fear, it has gone up to -
but despite this,
you will see that the property tax of the company
in Samman-2011 is more than last year's problem, it is
450 crores because the company's
income is 706 crores,
looking at this, the profit report of the company is
450 crores, which is more than last year, if you
net it off, then 239 crores
in previous years and this year it is 340 crores,
one and a half inch, send this message, then the company's
news in 2013, from 4000 to
12 crores, which have been given on airlines, then
in 2021  12183 crores, which is
slightly lower than last year,
at that level and if you see,
every figure of airlines has changed on a hair oil basis and
moving forward, now in train, if you
look at the operating profit, then there is a little minus
in plus minus and last year in 2008, look at
our profit of 1658 crores,
this property has got tax from
351 crores, if you look at it on year on year basis, then
last year it was 1954 crores,
here the net profit has increased from 353 crores to
1478 crores, if you look at the price, you will see that
every year the net
profit in train needs some plus minus,
so the company is
here, you will see in the network and then
in the company profit and at the place we have profit
up in train
and look at the share, last year it was 27.27.75,
this year 32.40 on share dividend
in India, this year and the highest
standard is 6%, if you
look at the company Cisco, then it has
60% in 10 years and compound  Profit growth
is 1000% in the last 12 months. Stock price has
shown 10 years of return on equity
and has given 30% return on equity and last year it was 22%. If you
look at the John Mayer Twenty One results in the balance sheet of the company, then the
company is almost every. But for the
last few years, the company has kept its
net worth of 85 crores, which is 21%. How can we look at the
company's shareholding pattern? If we look at the
March 2012 figures, the profit was 31.81 crore, the middle
price was 11.68 crore and the shareholding was 20%. We can
see the promoters' shareholding from
this. They have
reduced the shareholding by 51.5%
in 2018 and where the profit was 12.5% ​​in December 2016,
they have
made every quarter and this is for March 2018 and we will
also see the shareholding pattern of the company.  In 2004 it was 600
percent, that
it was reduced a bit, then and after starting to make from Swapna Dosh,
breaking the pride, it was reduced a bit in 2001, what about 11.6
percent, at the end of last year the School of
Public which was a little more, has
reduced till now in the last year and these sides are due to its
making, so
friends, these were the IPL awards, the
fundamentals of health insurance are good in the long term
and the companies were to launch the policy, this is
some TV policy launched, the company thought
that if you see, then you will get to see the benefit of the company from this group
and you will also get
to see the profit,
so please like, share and subscribe my
channel.